Guide to the Yale University Library Name/Title Card Catalog
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Man and nature (Box 4916)
- Man inside (Box 4917)
- Man who knew (Box 4918)
- Management, men, and values (Box 4919)
- Managing national accounts (Box 4920)
- Manchester (surname) (Box 4921)
- Manchus (Box 4922)
- Mandel, P. (Box 4923)
- Mandhana, B. (Box 4924)
- Manetti, A. (Box 4925)
- Mangin, C. (Box 4926)
- Mani, A. (Box 4927)
- Manila Bay (Box 4928)
- Mankes, J. (Box 4929)
- Mann, Gustav (Box 4930)
- Mann, Thomas, 1875-1955 (author) (Box 4931)
- Mann, Thomas, 1875-1955. Tod in Venedig (Box 4932)
- Mannchen, W. (Box 4933)
- Manning (Box 4934)
- Mannucci, C. (Box 4935)
- Manresa (Box 4936)
- Mansfield, K. (Box 4937)
- Manson, T. M. (Box 4938)
- Mantetsu ni ikito (Box 4939)
- Manual do lobo (Box 4940)
- Manuel (surname) (Box 4941)
- Manumission (Box 4942)
- Manwell, M. B. (Box 4943)
- Man'yoshu-Language (Box 4944)
- Manzoni, Alessandro -- (Subject) -- Addresses, essays, lectures (Box 4945)
- Mao, Tse-tung, 1893-1976 (M) (Box 4946)
- Mao, Tse-tung, 1893-1976 (subject) (continued) (Box 4947)
- Mao extrema (Box 4948)
- Map of the I. (Box 4949)
- Maquet, J. N. (Box 4950)
- Maran (Box 4951)
- Marbacher Q. (Box 4952)
- Marcaggi (Box 4953)
- Marcet (Box 4954)
- Marchand, R. (Box 4955)
- Marchis (Box 4956)
- Marcos (Box 4957)
- Marcus, D. (Box 4958)
- Marder, C. (Box 4959)
- Mares, G. (Box 4960)
- Margen, S. (Box 4961)
- Margon, G. (Box 4962)
- Maria de M. (Box 4963)
- Mariani, X. (Box 4964)
- Marie Antoinette (author) (Box 4965)
- Marignac (Box 4966)
- Marina Samad (Box 4967)
- Mariner's magazine (Box 4968)
- Marinov, V. (Box 4969)
- Maritain, Jacques, 1882- (author) (continued) (Box 4970)
- Mark (surname) (Box 4971)
- Markert, K. (Box 4972)
- Markham (Box 4973)
- Marko, K. (Box 4974)
- Marks, B. (Box 4975)
- Markwalder, H. (Box 4976)
- Marlowe, Christopher (author) (Box 4977)
- Marmontel, Jean Francois (subject) (Box 4978)
- Marotta, S. (Box 4979)
- Marquet, Yves (Box 4980)
- Marrant (Box 4981)
- Marriott, L. (Box 4982)
- Marschall, T. (Box 4983)
- Marsh, John, 1788-1868 (continued) (Box 4984)
- Marshall, D. (Box 4985)
- Marshall, Louis (Box 4986)
- Marsidi (Box 4987)
- Martel, P. (Box 4988)
- Marti, Jose, 1853-1895 (author) (Box 4989)
- Martial, P. (Box 4990)
- Martin, Charles Lee (Box 4991)
- Martin, Georg (Box 4992)
- Martin, Jean Claude (Box 4993)
- Martin, P. (Box 4994)
- Martin, V. (Box 4995)
- Martin Luther-Bund (Box 4996)
- Martinek, K. (Box 4997)
- Martinez, M. (Box 4998)
- Martinez Marina (Box 4999)
- Martini, Joseph (Box 5000)
- Martinson, G. (Box 5001)
- Marty, Maurice (Box 5002)
- Marulayya, S. (Box 5003)
- Marvin, G. (Box 5004)
- Marx, Karl (author) Kapital (continued) (Box 5005)
- Marx, Karl (subject) (J) (Box 5006)
- Marx, Karl-Bibliography (Box 5007)
- Marx (titles, etc.) Marxism in the... (Box 5008)
- Mary, Virgin-Art (Box 5009)
- Mary, Queen of Scots, 1542-1587 (M) (Box 5010)
- Maryland (State) (author) (Box 5011)
- Maryland Geological Survey (Box 5012)
- Masa Bergolak (Box 5013)
- Masaryk, Tomas Garrigue (Pamphlets) (Box 5014)
- Mascle, J. (Box 5015)
- Maseres, F. (Box 5016)
- Masked media (Box 5017)
- Mason, Bruce (Box 5018)
- Mason, Lowell (Box 5019)
- Masorah (texts) (Box 5020)
- Mass transit (Box 5021)
- Massachusetts. Cambridge (Box 5022)
- Massachusetts. General Court (author) (Box 5023)
- Massachusetts. Special Commission (Box 5024)
- Massachusetts Historical Society (subject) (Box 5025)
- Massachusetts Magazine (Box 5026)
- Masselin, Pierre (Box 5027)
- Massillon (Box 5028)
- Masson, I. (Box 5029)
- Master of (Box 5030)
- Masters, J. (Box 5031)
- Masuda, Ko (Box 5032)
- Matamoros (Box 5033)
- Mater Europa (Box 5034)
- Materialization (Box 5035)
- Materialy i prace... (Box 5036)
- Mates (Box 5037)
- Mathematical sociolgy (Box 5038)
- Mather, Cotton. Magnalia Christi (Box 5039)
- Matheson (Box 5040)
- Mathews, Shailer (Box 5041)
- Mathon, Alix (Box 5042)
- Matisse (Box 5043)
- Matraja (Box 5044)
- Matsuda, Ryo (Box 5045)
- Matsumoto, Shinpachiro (Box 5046)
- Matsuoka, Jack (Box 5047)
- Mattani (Box 5048)
- Matthes (Box 5049)
- Matthews, James (Box 5050)
- Matthiessen, Francis Otto (Box 5051)
- Maturana, Sergio (Box 5052)
- Mau (Box 5053)
- Maugham (Box 5054)
- Maun (Author and title enties interfiled) (Box 5055)
- Maurel (Box 5056)
- Mauriac, Francois (subject) (Box 5057)
- Mauritius (Box 5058)
- Maurras (Box 5059)
- Maverick family (Box 5060)
- Max, Wendy (Box 5061)
- Maximilian, emperor of Mexico (subject) (Box 5062)
- Maxwell, J. H. (Box 5063)
- May, H. (Box 5064)
- Maya (Box 5065)
- Mayer (Box 5066)
- Mayer, Josef (Box 5067)
- Mayfair Agency (Box 5068)
- Mayne (Box 5069)
- Mayor (titles, etc.) (Box 5070)
- Mazakute, Paul (Box 5071)
- Mazon, M. (Box 5072)
- Mazzini, Giuseppe (subject) (R) (Box 5073)
- Me lo conto... (Box 5074)
- Meade (Box 5075)
- Meaning of Evolution (Box 5076)
- Measurement of s. (Box 5077)
- Mechanik (Box 5078)
- Meconnu… (Box 5079)
- Medellin (Colombia) (Box 5080)
- Medical examiner (Box 5081)
- Medici, House of (Box 5082)
- Medieval and (Box 5083)
- Medina (Box 5084)
- Meditation upon (Box 5085)
- Medunarodno javno... (Box 5086)
- Meeker (Box 5087)
- Meeting (Box 5088)
- Meginnes (Box 5089)
- Mehring (Box 5090)
- Mei-kuo hsing (Box 5091)
- Mei tsai... (Box 5092)
- Meier, N. (Box 5093)
- Meiji Amerika (Box 5094)
- Meiji Shoin (Box 5095)
- Meillan (Box 5096)
- Meinhof (Box 5097)
- Meisel, R. (Box 5098)
- Meister, I. (Box 5099)
- Mekeel (Box 5100)
- Melanchthon, Philipp (author) (Box 5101)
- Melanges ecologiques (Box 5102)
- Melchior Lechter (Box 5103)
- Melibea (Box 5104)
- Meller (Box 5105)
- Mellone (Box 5106)
- Melomaniacs (Box 5107)
- Melville, Herman (Box 5108)
- Melzer, Y. (Box 5109)
- Memo for spring (Box 5110)
- Memoires de (Box 5111)
- Memoires, regles... (Box 5112)
- Memoirs of the life (Box 5113)
- Memoria y balance (Box 5114)
- Memorial volume (Box 5115)
- Memorie sacre... (Box 5116)
- Men of (Box 5117)
- Menander, of Athens (titles, catalogued after Dec. 1980) (Box 5118)
- Mencken, Henry Louis, 1880-1956 (continued) (Box 5119)
- Mendelsohn, F. (Box 5120)
- Mendes, F. (Box 5121)
- Mendl, B. (Box 5122)
- Menefee, L. A. (Box 5123)
- Menezes, Ruy (Box 5124)
- Meng, Wan-fu (Box 5125)
- Menius, E. (Box 5126)
- Menot, M. (Box 5127)
- Mensching (Box 5128)
- Mentzel, O. (Box 5129)
- Mer (Box 5130)
- Mercanton (Box 5131)
- Merchant (titles, etc.) (Box 5132)
- Mercklin (Box 5133)
- Meredith, George (author) (Box 5134)
- Merg, J. (Box 5135)
- Merimee, Prosper (author) (Box 5136)
- Merkel (Box 5137)
- Merlette (Box 5138)
- Merriam, E. (Box 5139)
- Merrill, W. (Box 5140)
- Merry Purim (Box 5141)
- Merton, Thomas, 1915-1968 (continued) (Box 5142)
- Merzdorf (Box 5143)
- Mesick (Box 5144)
- Messedaglia (Box 5145)
- Messner, H. (Box 5146)
- Metal man (Box 5147)
- Metastasio (Box 5148)
- Meteorology on... (Box 5149)
- Methodist Episcopal church (author) (Box 5150)
- Methodius, of Olympus, Saint, d. 311 (Box 5151)
- Metin (Box 5152)
- Metropolis in (Box 5153)
- Metropolitan Museum of Art, New York. Jewelry (Box 5154)
- Mettais (Box 5155)
- Metzger, Wolfgang (Box 5156)
- Meusch (Box 5157)
- Mexico (author) (Box 5158)
- Mexico (By date) (Laws, etc.), 1848-1851 (Box 5159)
- Mexico. Direccion (Box 5160)
- Mexico. Presidente (continued) (Box 5161)
- Mexico. Secretaria de Relaciones Exteriores (Box 5162)
- Mexico City (Box 5163)
- Meyer, Adolf H. (Box 5164)
- Meyer, Erich (Box 5165)
- Meyer, Hugo (Box 5166)
- Meyer, Paul, 1840-1917 (Box 5167)
- Meyer von Knonau (Box 5168)
- Meynell, E. (Box 5169)
- Mezhdunarodnaia n. (Box 5170)
- Mezzogiorno normanno (Box 5171)
- Mi tsung ta... (Box 5172)
- Miara ost. (Box 5173)
- Michael R. (Box 5174)
- Michalet, L. (Box 5175)
- Michel, E. (Box 5176)
- Michel Angelo Buonarroti (subject) (Box 5177)
- Michell (Box 5178)
- Michigan. Board (Box 5179)
- Michigan. Legislature (Box 5180)
- Michigan log cabins (Box 5181)
- Michitsuna no Haha (Box 5182)
- Mickley (Box 5183)
- Micrographics (Box 5184)
- Middle East (titles, phrases, etc.) (Box 5185)
- Middlebury (Box 5186)
- Middleton, Thomas, d. 1627 (author) (Box 5187)
- Midrash (Box 5188)
- Mid-western banker... (Box 5189)
- Mien ch'an (Box 5190)
- Miftah W. (Box 5191)
- Migrantes no... (Box 5192)
- Mihaly, J. (Box 5193)
- Mike, N. (Box 5194)
- Mikel'son, V.A. (Box 5195)
- Mikromat Dresden (Box 5196)
- Milan. F. (Box 5197)
- Milbank (Box 5198)
- Miles, G. (Box 5199)
- Milham, W. (Box 5200)
- Militarists (Box 5201)
- Military veteran (Box 5202)
- Mill, W. (Box 5203)
- Millas, F. (Box 5204)
- Miller, Arthur (Box 5205)
- Miller, Edward (Box 5206)
- Miller, Henry, 1891- (continued) (Box 5207)
- Miller, Joaquin (Box 5208)
- Miller, Mary (Box 5209)
- Miller, Ron (Box 5210)
- Miller, William M. (Box 5211)
- Millikan (Box 5212)
- Mills, C. Wright (Box 5213)
- Mills family (Box 5214)
- Milner (Box 5215)
- Milosz, O.V. (Box 5216)
- Milton, John. Lycidas (Box 5217)
- Milton, John (subject) (F) (Box 5218)
- Milwaukee (titles, etc.) (Box 5219)
- Min chu (Box 5220)
- Min Shin (Box 5221)
- Minami Manshu Tetsudo Kabushiki Kaisha (Box 5222)
- Minasian, R. (Box 5223)
- Minding, F. (Box 5224)
- Mineralogical Society of America (Box 5225)
- Min ching i (Box 5226)
- Ming T (Box 5227)
- Mini informe (Box 5228)
- Ministerium S. (Box 5229)
- Minnesaenger (Box 5230)
- Minnesota Historical Society (author) (Box 5231)
- Minor, K. (Box 5232)
- Minsk oblast (Box 5233)
- Minutes of the... (Box 5234)
- Mira, C. (Box 5235)
- Miram, Helga-M (Box 5236)
- Miret, Pedro F. (Box 5237)
- Mironov, K (Box 5238)
- Mirzabekian, Zhora M. (Box 5239)
- Miscellanea storico-l (Box 5240)
- Miserez, H. (Box 5241)
- Mishnah, A. (Box 5242)
- Mision providencial (Box 5243)
- Miss Lonelyhearts (Box 5244)
- Missionary confraternity... (Box 5245)
- Mississippi Central... (Box 5246)
- Missouri. Laws, s... (Box 5247)
- Mister Fisherman (Box 5248)
- Mistral, Gabriela. L. (Box 5249)
- Mitani, Yoshiaki (Box 5250)
- Mitchell, Edwin V (Box 5251)
- Mitchell, Otis C. (Box 5252)
- Mitchell, Walter (Box 5253)
- Mitjana y Gordon... (Box 5254)
- Mitrofanov, P. (Box 5255)
- Mittarelli, Giovanni B. (Box 5256)
- Mittelhoelzer, Edgar (Box 5257)
- Miura, Ayako (Box 5258)
- Miyake, Hitoshi (Box 5259)
- Miyatake, Gaikotsu (Box 5260)
- Mizner, Addison (Box 5261)
- Mladezi (Box 5262)
- Mo-Kyo kokoki (Box 5263)
- Moberly, George H (Box 5264)
- Mockenhaupt, Hubert (Box 5265)
- Modelo politico... (Box 5266)
- Modern Asian... (Box 5267)
- Modern developments... (Box 5268)
- Modern Language... (Box 5269)
- Modern nationalities (Box 5270)
- Modern theatre... (Box 5271)
- Modernization and social... (Box 5272)
- Modoc Indian War (Box 5273)
- Moehlig, Wilhelm J (Box 5274)
- Moeller, Wilhelm (Box 5275)
- Moeschal, Jacques (Box 5276)
- Mogil, Norman (Box 5277)
- Mohand ou Mohand (Box 5278)
- Mohr, Larry (Box 5279)
- Moise, A. (Box 5280)
- Mokslo Kulturos (Box 5281)
- Molecular basis (Box 5282)
- Molesworth, Mary L. (Box 5283)
- Moliere, Jean B. (Box 5284)
- Molina, M. (Box 5285)
- Molitor, J. (Box 5286)
- Molly Moriarty (Box 5287)
- Moltmann, J. (Box 5288)
- Mommsen, T. (Box 5289)
- Monahan, B. (Box 5290)
- Moncada, J. (Box 5291)
- Le Monde (Box 5292)
- Monet, C. (Box 5293)
- Money, employment (Box 5294)
- Mongolia Society (Box 5295)
- Monjo, E. (Box 5296)
- Monnier, A. (Box 5297)
- Monografias Agrarias (Box 5298)
- Monograph of (Box 5299)
- Monographien zur (Box 5300)
- Monographs on (Box 5301)
- Monroe, H. (Box 5302)
- Monson, John M. (Box 5303)
- Montague, Charles E. (Box 5304)
- Montale, E. (Box 5305)
- Montana. Bureau (Box 5306)
- Monte, A. (Box 5307)
- Monteiro L. (Box 5308)
- Montero y V. (Box 5309)
- Montet, A. (Box 5310)
- Montgomery, H. (Box 5311)
- Montherlant, H. (Box 5312)
- Monticelli, A. (Box 5313)
- Montreal. Board of (Box 5314)
- Monument de (Box 5315)
- Monumenta transsilvanica (Box 5316)
- Moody, E. (Box 5317)
- Moon, P. (Box 5318)
- Moore, B. (Box 5319)
- Moore, E. (Box 5320)
- Moore, H. (Box 5321)
- Moore, J. (Box 5322)
- Moore, R. (Box 5323)
- Moore, Z. (Box 5324)
- Mora, pseud. (Box 5325)
- Moral development (Box 5326)
- Morales Olaya, R. (Box 5327)
- Morand, S. (Box 5328)
- Moravian Church (Box 5329)
- Mordovtsev, D. (Box 5330)
- More, Sir T. (Box 5331)
- Moreau, E. (Box 5332)
- Moreiras, Spain (Box 5333)
- Morenas, L. (Box 5334)
- Moret, A. (Box 5335)
- Morgan, A. (Box 5336)
- Morgan, H. (Box 5337)
- Morgan, O. (Box 5338)
- Morgenroth, A. (Box 5339)
- Mori, N. (Box 5340)
- Morikawa, H. (Box 5341)
- Morison, J. (Box 5342)
- Moriya, H. (Box 5343)
- Morley, H. (Box 5344)
- Morning glory (Box 5345)
- Morone, S. (Box 5346)
- Morrell, J. (Box 5347)
- Morris, Edward E. (Box 5348)
- Morris, L. (Box 5349)
- Morris, W. (Box 5350)
- Morrison, C. (Box 5351)
- Morrissey, L. (Box 5352)
- Morse, J. (Box 5353)
- Mort, E. (Box 5354)
- Mortimer, A. (Box 5355)
- Morton, N. (Box 5356)
- Mosaiken, Fresken, M. (Box 5357)
- Moscow, A... (Box 5358)
- Moscow. TSentral... (Box 5359)
- Moser, E. (Box 5360)
- Moses, J. (Box 5361)
- Moskin, J. (Box 5362)
- Moskovskii S. (Box 5363)
- Moss, J. (Box 5364)
- The most wanted... (Box 5365)
- Motet, A. (Box 5366)
- Motivation in (Box 5367)
- Mots et (Box 5368)
- Motto, R. (Box 5369)
- Moulian, T. (Box 5370)
- Mount, A. (Box 5371)
- The mountain s... (Box 5372)
- Mourlot, F. (Box 5373)
- Mouvement m. (Box 5374)
- Movimiento de L. (Box 5375)
- Mowry, G. (Box 5376)
- Mozambik (Box 5377)
- Mozejko, E. (Box 5378)
- Msiri, King of (Box 5379)
- Mu'ayyad S. (Box 5380)
- Mudhakkirat (Box 5381)
- Muelder, H. (Box 5382)
- Mueller, E. (Box 5383)
- Mueller, G. (Box 5384)
- Mueller, J. (Box 5385)
- Mueller, M. (Box 5386)
- Mueller, W. (Box 5387)
- Muench, V. (Box 5388)
- Muendler, E. (Box 5389)
- Muenzer, H. (Box 5390)
- Mughniyah, M. (Box 5391)
- Muhammad, the (Box 5392)
- Muhammad b. (Box 5393)
- Muhammad K. (Box 5394)
- Muhlenberg, H. (Box 5395)
- Muir, Mrs. W. (Box 5396)
- Mujica L. (Box 5397)
- Mukhopadhyay, A. (Box 5398)
- Mulford, A. (Box 5399)
- Muller, F. (Box 5400)
- Mulot, A. (Box 5401)
- Multiple-factor a. (Box 5402)
- Mumpton, F. (Box 5403)
- Muncker, F. (Box 5404)
- Mundy, J. (Box 5405)
- Municipal a. (Box 5406)
- Munkacsy, M. (Box 5407)
- Munro, B. (Box 5408)
- Munson, J. (Box 5409)
- Murad, Z. (Box 5410)
- Muraro, M. (Box 5411)
- Muratori, L. (Box 5412)
- The murder of (Box 5413)
- Murga, F. (Box 5414)
- Muroga, N. (Box 5415)
- Murphy, G. (Box 5416)
- Murray, A. (Box 5417)
- Murray, J. (Box 5418)
- Murray, R. (Box 5419)
- Murtagh, W. (Box 5420)
- Musarum a. (Box 5421)
- Musee d'art (Box 5422)
- Musee des A. (Box 5423)
- Musee du p. (Box 5424)
- Musee Picasso (Box 5425)
- Museo d'arte (Box 5426)
- Museo naz. (Box 5427)
- Museum der B. (Box 5428)
- Museum Nasional (Box 5429)
- Museum of F. (Box 5430)
- Museum of M. (Box 5431)
- Museumsverein D. (Box 5432)
- Music in B. (Box 5433)
- Musik der Z. (Box 5434)
- Muslim B. (Box 5435)
- Musset, G. (Box 5436)
- Mustafa C. (Box 5437)
- Mutanabbi (Box 5438)
- Mutterer, F. (Box 5439)
- Muze'on T. (Box 5440)
- My best g. (Box 5441)
- My life in the... (Box 5442)
- Mya. daun Hsaya-do (Box 5443)
- Myers, H. (Box 5444)
- Mykytenko, O. (Box 5445)
- Myron (Box 5446)
- Mysterious D. (Box 5447)
- Myth of the B. (Box 5448)
- N., R. (Box 5449)
- N.I.S. (Box 5450)
- NU-serien: B. (Box 5451)
- Na pustyre (Box 5452)
- Nabokov (Box 5453)
- Nachman (Box 5454)
- Nada, I. (Box 5455)
- Nadler, J. (Box 5456)
- Nafe (Box 5457)
- Nagano-ken seito shi (Box 5458)
- Nagato, T. (Box 5459)
- Nagler (Box 5460)
- Nahar, A. (Box 5461)
- Naidel, M. (Box 5462)
- Naisawald, L. (Box 5463)
- Najm, K. (Box 5464)
- Nakaji, S. (Box 5465)
- Nakamura, N. (Box 5466)
- Nakano, T. (Box 5467)
- Naked society (Box 5468)
- Namba, H. (Box 5469)
- Namora, F. (Box 5470)
- Nan-hai-sou (Box 5471)
- Nan wei (Box 5472)
- Nandino (Box 5473)
- Nanson, A. (Box 5474)
- Naosaku, S. (Box 5475)
- Napoleon (author) (O) (Box 5476)
- Napoleon-Bibliography (Box 5477)
- Napoleon-Invasion of Russia (T) (Box 5478)
- Napolitano, L. (Box 5479)
- Naramoto, Tatsuya (Box 5480)
- Nardi (Box 5481)
- Narodna biblioteka. Kiril i Metodii (Box 5482)
- Narodno p. (Box 5483)
- Narragansett (Box 5484)
- Narsai (Box 5485)
- Nase Slovensko (Box 5486)
- Nash, Philip C. (Box 5487)
- Nasilje (Box 5488)
- Nassef, E.S. (Box 5489)
- Natal mercury (Box 5490)
- Nathan, I. (Box 5491)
- Nation and l. (Box 5492)
- National accounts studies (Box 5493)
- National Association Gazette (Box 5494)
- National Association of Real Estate Boards (Box 5495)
- National Board of Medical Examiners (Box 5496)
- National calendar (Box 5497)
- National City Bank (Box 5498)
- National conference of... (Box 5499)
- National congress (Box 5500)
- National Council of Teachers of English (Box 5501)
- National Education Association (Box 5502)
- National Endowment (Box 5503)
- National Gallery of Art (Box 5504)
- National Gallery of V. (Box 5505)
- National Indian (Box 5506)
- National Institute of C. (Box 5507)
- National Labor (Box 5508)
- National life (Box 5509)
- National Museum (Box 5510)
- National Peace (Box 5511)
- National prison (Box 5512)
- National Research Council (U.S.) Advisory Committee (continued) (Box 5513)
- National Research Council (U.S.). Committee on National Statistics (Box 5514)
- National Research Council (U.S.). Foreign Field (Box 5515)
- National Research Council (Canada) (Box 5516)
- National Science Foundation (U.S.) (continued) (Box 5517)
- National society for the study of education (Box 5518)
- National survey maps (Box 5519)
- National tuberculosis (Box 5520)
- National Zoological Park (U.S.) (Box 5521)
- Nationalsozialistische deutsche Arbeiter Partei. H. (Box 5522)
- Nationalsozialistischer Lehrerbund (Box 5523)
- NATO ASI series. Series D (Box 5524)
- NATO Advanced Study Institute on New D. (Box 5525)
- Natorp, Paul Gerhard (Box 5526)
- Natucci, A. (Box 5527)
- Natural resources and e. (Box 5528)
- The nature of h. (Box 5529)
- Naturzustand und (Box 5530)
- Nauchnyi k. (Box 5531)
- Naujoks, E. (Box 5532)
- Naundorf, K. (Box 5533)
- Naval research (Box 5534)
- Navas, J. (Box 5535)
- Nawadir (Box 5536)
- Nazario, L. (Box 5537)
- Ne obra. (Box 5538)
- Neapolitan gold (Box 5539)
- Nebraska. Emerg. (Box 5540)
- Neck, R. (Box 5541)
- Nederlands Gen. (Box 5542)
- Nederlandsche Oost... (Box 5543)
- Needham, J. (Box 5544)
- Neff, J. (Box 5545)
- Negri, G. (Box 5546)
- Negro's mem. (Box 5547)
- Neider, C. (Box 5548)
- Neilson, A. (Box 5549)
- Nekotorye v. (Box 5550)
- Nelli, R. (Box 5551)
- Nelson, J. (Box 5552)
- Nelson and (Box 5553)
- Nemirna g. (Box 5554)
- Neobkhodimyi r. (Box 5555)
- Nephrology (Box 5556)
- Nernst, C. (Box 5557)
- Nerval, p. (Box 5558)
- Nest of the... (Box 5559)
- Netherlands (Kingdom, 1815-) Central (Box 5560)
- Netherlands (Kingdom, 1815-) Department (continued) (Box 5561)
- Netibandit 2509 (Box 5562)
- Neu, K. (Box 5563)
- Neue Apologie... (Box 5564)
- Neue praxis (Box 5565)
- Neues (Box 5566)
- Neukirch, B. (Box 5567)
- Neumann, Kaspar (Box 5568)
- Neurath (Box 5569)
- Neuss, E. (Box 5570)
- Nevada. Legislature (continued) (Box 5571)
- Nevesta (Box 5572)
- Nevolin, P.A. (Box 5573)
- New art (Box 5574)
- New Caledonia (Box 5575)
- New deal message (Box 5576)
- New England (colony) (Box 5577)
- New England palladium (Box 5578)
- New Fabian Research Bureau, (Great Britain) (Box 5579)
- New Hampshire, Constitutional convention (Box 5580)
- New Haven. Ordinances, etc. (Box 5581)
- New Haven, Conn. (author) (Box 5582)
- New Haven tax book (Box 5583)
- New Jersey (State) (author) (Box 5584)
- New Jersey. State prison (Box 5585)
- New leaders (Box 5586)
- New Mexico. Department of Education (Box 5587)
- New Oratory (Box 5588)
- New pictorial... (Box 5589)
- New scientists (Box 5590)
- New Spalding club (Box 5591)
- New universal (Box 5592)
- New York (City) Anthon memorial church (Box 5593)
- New York (City) City affairs committee (Box 5594)
- New York (City) Fire department (Box 5595)
- New York (City) Metropolitan Opera (Box 5596)
- New York (City) Society of (Box 5597)
- New York (State) Board of Agriculture (Box 5598)
- New York (State) Civil service law (Box 5599)
- New York (State) Department of agriculture and markets (Box 5600)
- New York (State) Legislature (author) (Box 5601)
- New York (State) State hospital (Box 5602)
- New York Academy of Sciences (Box 5603)
- New York Daily (Box 5604)
- New York Journal (Box 5605)
- New York Public library. Naval architecture (Box 5606)
- New York state conference (Box 5607)
- New York Times (continued) (Box 5608)
- New York Weekly (Box 5609)
- New Zealand. Department of Statistics (continued) (Box 5610)
- New Zealand institute (Box 5611)
- Newberry, P. (Box 5612)
- Newcastle journal (Box 5613)
- Newell, Edward Theodore (Box 5614)
- Newi, W. (Box 5615)
- Newman, John Henry (author) (Box 5616)
- Newman, Penny (Box 5617)
- News cavalcade (Box 5618)
- Newspapers in N. (Box 5619)
- Newton, Isaac, Sir (subject) (G) (Box 5620)
- Ney (Box 5621)
- Nghiem Duy (Box 5622)
- Nguyen, J. (Box 5623)
- Nhokwara, T. (Box 5624)
- Niagara news (Box 5625)
- Nicaragua. Ministerio de economica (Box 5626)
- Nichi-Bei kosho (Box 5627)
- Nichol, John Pringle (Box 5628)
- Nicholls, J. (Box 5629)
- Nichols, R. (Box 5630)
- Nicholson, Peter (Box 5631)
- Nicol, E.P. (Box 5632)
- Nicolaus (surname) (Box 5633)
- Nicolson, Harold George (Box 5634)
- Niebuhr, H.R. (Box 5635)
- Niedersachsen (Box 5636)
- Nielsen, E. (Box 5637)
- Niemi, T. (Box 5638)
- Nieto (Box 5639)
- Nietzsche, Friedrich Wilhelm (subject) (M) (Box 5640)
- Nieuwenhuysen, W.L. (Box 5641)
- Nigeria. Federal Ministry of Education (Box 5642)
- Nigerian outlook (Box 5643)
- Nightmare of (Box 5644)
- Nihon Bungaku Kenkyukai (Box 5645)
- Nihon Fashizumu kyoiku (Box 5646)
- Nihon gogengaku (Box 5647)
- Nihon kanjion gairon (Box 5648)
- Nihon kindai bungaku shi (Box 5649)
- Nihon kokudo taikei (Box 5650)
- Nihon Kyosanto-Addresses, essays, lectures (continued) (Box 5651)
- Nihon no bungaku (Box 5652)
- Nihon no kotoba (Box 5653)
- Nihon no shika (Box 5654)
- Nihon rekishi nyumon (Box 5655)
- Nihon Shakaito (Box 5656)
- Nihon shoki (continued) (Box 5657)
- Nihon zasshi (Box 5658)
- Nihonkai chii (Box 5659)
- Nikaido, Y. (Box 5660)
- Nikolaev, K.M. (Box 5661)
- Nikonova, I. (Box 5662)
- Nilsson, S.T. (Box 5663)
- Nine hundred i. (Box 5664)
- Ninham, John (Box 5665)
- Nippon no o. (Box 5666)
- Nishibayashi, S. (Box 5667)
- Nishitani, K. (Box 5668)
- Nitchu (Box 5669)
- Nittka (Box 5670)
- Nixon, I. (Box 5671)
- Njegovan (Box 5672)
- No more (Box 5673)
- Noake (Box 5674)
- Noble, J. (Box 5675)
- Noche, R. (Box 5676)
- Noe, L. (Box 5677)
- Noerdlich (Box 5678)
- Noguchi, U. (Box 5679)
- Noizet (Box 5680)
- Nollau (Box 5681)
- Nominal C. (Box 5682)
- Nones (Box 5683)
- Nonsenseorship (Box 5684)
- Norbert (Box 5685)
- Nordens l. (Box 5686)
- Nordisk e. (Box 5687)
- Nordmann (Box 5688)
- Norge under H. (Box 5689)
- Norma (Box 5690)
- Normandy (surname) (Box 5691)
- Norris, K. (Box 5692)
- Norske videnskaps-akademi i Oslo (Box 5693)
- North American company (Box 5694)
- North Atlantic Treaty Organization. Science Committee (Box 5695)
- North Borneo (Box 5696)
- North Carolina. Unemployment... (Box 5697)
- North Dakota. State... (Box 5698)
- North west U. (Box 5699)
- Northern (Box 5700)
- Northern Methodism (Box 5701)
- Northern Sotho (Box 5702)
- Northwest Pacific (Box 5703)
- Norton, Anne (Box 5704)
- Norton company (Box 5705)
- Norway. Statistisk Sentralbyra (continued) (Box 5706)
- Norwich (titles, etc.) (Box 5707)
- Noson s. (Box 5708)
- Not to (Box 5709)
- Notes (Box 5710)
- Notestein, F. (Box 5711)
- Noticioso (Box 5712)
- Notre q. (Box 5713)
- Nourrisson, J. (Box 5714)
- Nouvelle collection (Box 5715)
- Nova prosa (Box 5716)
- Novak, Michael (Box 5717)
- Novel p. (Box 5718)
- Novgorod. (Box 5719)
- Novo almanach (Box 5720)
- Novy, A. (Box 5721)
- Nowell (Box 5722)
- Noyes, N. (Box 5723)
- Nu ta tang (Box 5724)
- Nuclear safeguards (Box 5725)
- Nuestra musica (Box 5726)